worldisraelnews.com 2018-03-23

# Privacy Policy - World Israel News

**Privacy Policy and Legal Information**

We collect information from you ONLY if and when you register on our site, subscribe to our newsletter or fill out a web form.

When registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name and/or e-mail address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously without providing personal information.

Like most websites, we use cookies and/or web beacons to enhance your experience, gather general visitor information, and track visits to our website. Please refer to the ‘do we use cookies?’ section below for information about cookies and how we use them.

We may use third-party advertising companies (such as Google) to place ads on our website. These companies may use non-personal information (excluding your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

* Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.  
* Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.  
* Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

**What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

• To personalize your experience  
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)

• To improve our website  
(we continually strive to improve our website based on the information and feedback we receive from you)

• To improve our service to you  
(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your requests and needs)

• To send Israel-related email updates

The email address you provide will be used to send Israel-related information from WIN and its affiliates.

If you decide to become a member of our mailing list, you will receive emails that may include Israel-related news, updates, promotions and/or related charity or service information.

If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include unsubscribe links at the bottom of each email. We maintain distinct, segmented lists, using different email marketing systems and databases, so that it is possible, for example, to unsubscribe from promotions and/or webinar notifications, but still receive regular newsletters. You may unsubscribe from all email updates by clicking the unsubscribe link in each segmented list.

**Do we use cookies?**

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do NOT sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted affiliates who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

**Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act).

**Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our websites privacy policy.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy and Legal Disclosures**

All changes to our privacy policy and legal disclosures will be updated on this page.
